http://www.informationliteracy.org/content/show/privacy_policy

Search Keyword:
Grade Level:
Search in:
Create Account
Forgot password?
Sponsors
Privacy PolicyThe S.O.S. for Information Literacy project (S.O.S.) is committed to protecting the privacy of its members. This policy addresses the collection, use, disclosure and modification of information pertaining to you. Collection of Information:Personally identifiable information (PII) collected from you includes your name, email address, workplace address and location, position, number of years in your position, and grades taught. This information is submitted voluntarily by you to S.O.S. in order to participate in the resources provided on the S.O.S. site which includes reviewing/downloading lesson plans and media, participating in possible forums, using the planned virtual reference desks and sharing your work with members of the education community. Cookies, small bits of information placed on your computer, are used to help you track your lesson plans submitted, in progress, and completed. cookies can also be used to store your login status and to generally make your interaction with the site more enjoyable. Anonymous information may also be collected on site visits to provide aggregate information such as subject areas most searched, most used features, etc. This knowledge will be used to evaluate and provide suggestions for improvement of the resource.  Use of Information:The information collected from you will be used for a number of purposes. They are to:1) Provide you a username based on your email address2) Inform you of the evaluation status of lesson plans you submit3) Provide S.O.S. staff with general user demographics for reporting purposes.4) Credit you on lesson plans submitted by you to S.O.S. for Information Literacy. Such credit includes your full name, position, and affiliation. 5) Email you general information about the S.O.S. project including occasional newsletters, project announcements, user surveys, etc. Disclosure of Information:S.O.S. will never disclose your PII to advertisers or any other third parties. Exception to this would only be in the case that S.O.S. was absorbed by another educational organization or transferred to another institution. Only the information regarding your credits (#4 above) will be disclosed on lesson plans submitted by you for public access on the database. S.O.S. will not your use PII for any other purposes other than what has been described above unless we obtain your permission. Changing Your Personal Information:You may modify your personal information at any time by linking to your registration page from the LOGIN screen. You may also change your password at any time. Instructions for doing so appear on your LOGIN page, as well. Passwords are encrypted both in transit and when stored within the S.O.S. databases. Other:The S.O.S. site includes links to other sites which it deems may be helpful to its users. S.O.S. is not responsible for the privacy practices of other Internet sites. Visitors to outside sites should check the respective sites' privacy policies before providing personal information. Please check back to review this policy as S.O.S. may revise from time to time based on changes in the law, collection and use practices, and/or modifications of the features and technology associated with the site. Contact Information:If you have any concerns regarding this privacy policy, you may contact Marilyn P. Arnone or Ruth V. Small at the Center for Digital Literacy at cdl@syr.edu. Or call 315-443-6144.
Questions or comments? Contact DataMomentum team for general information
regarding the website itself. Posted 3/7/06 Privacy Policy Copyright Policy
Website by Data Momentum, Inc.
